ihigh.com 2014-12-27

# Volar Video Help - Privacy

At Volar Video, Inc., we are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Volar Video does not solicit any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Accordingly, children under 13 years old may be restricted from participating in certain activities and transactions on Volar Video, Inc.

Volar Video, Inc. works with (and may provide links to) third party sites that offer features described on Volar Video, Inc. Such third parties may permit children under the age of 13 to register on their sites in accordance with their respective privacy policies. However, Volar Video, Inc. does not knowingly obtain, retain or use information from anyone who indicates that they are under 13 years old.

Please read this Privacy Policy ("Policy") for an explanation of how we will treat your personal information. By using a Volar Video, Inc. Web Site, you consent to the collection and use of personal information as outlined in this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use our site. If we make any material changes to the Policy, those changes will be posted here so that you are always aware of what personal information is collected, how that information is used, and under what circumstances that information may be disclosed. Since this Policy may change from time to time, you should check back periodically. Your continued use of Volar Video following the posting of changes to the Policy will signal your acceptance of such changes. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Policy, please contact Volar Video at (859) 309-4307.

### 1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the site

As stated above, Volar Video, Inc. does not solicit any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Volar Video, Inc. does not collect personally identifiable information through the site unless you provide that information. Information that may be required for certain parts of the Web Site may vary but will typically include your first and last name; address including city, state, zip code and country; complete date of birth; and e-mail address; and, in the case of making purchases, a credit card number and expiration date. You may also be requested to provide a username and password for certain features. Volar Video, Inc. will maintain all of the personal information submitted by you in secured servers behind corporate firewalls.

### 2\. The organization collecting the information

Volar Video, Inc. is located at 325 West Main Street, Suite 300, Lexington, KY 40507. Please contact Volar Video at (859) 309-4307.

### 3\. How the information is used

Volar Video, Inc. may use information provided at registration or information obtained through third parties as your intention to sign up for one of our contests or offers. The use of information provided at registration or obtained through third parties may also be provided to Volar Video corporate sponsors if we have so notified you on our site. Volar Video, Inc. uses "cookie" technology. Cookies are pieces of information transferred to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Such technology is an industry standard and is used by most major Web sites. Volar Video, Inc. will never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. In order to effectively use the site and some of its features, your browser must accept cookies.

Users should be aware that Volar Video, Inc. cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for Volar Video, Inc. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept cookies; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features available on Volar Video Web Sites.

Volar Video, Inc. may, from time to time, use third party tools that help it understand how visitors engage with the site. Volar Video, Inc. may share the data collected by such services with third parties in order to obtain web analytics and benchmarking services.

Volar Video, Inc. is currently using Google Analytics and/or other analytics programs for this purpose. Users can review the full Google Analytics Privacy Policy regarding how Google uses and processes Data, seen [here __](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). When you visit a site, such as this Web Site, Google uses the information it receives from the site for a number of reasons, including making advertising more effective and providing reports of advertising activity to advertisers and websites hosting the ads.

As an example, Google Analytics collects and provides data on users’ demographics (for example, users’ Age and gender) and users’ interests (such as affinity categories, in-market segments, and other behavior related interest categories) such that Volar Video, Inc. may determine usage trends for this Web Site. If you do not want Google Analytics to collect this information, there are options for you to “opt out” of Google Analytics by going to [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ __](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/), which provides a Browser Add-on that prevents user data from being used by Google Analytics. If you wish to opt-out, download and install the add-on for your web browser.

Additionally, Volar Video, Inc. tracks certain general usage pattern information, including what pages people visit and how long they have been registered users. Volar Video, Inc. may log users' IP addresses (the group of four numbers separated by periods, such as 123.45.64.89, that identifies a particular host computer) for the purposes of system administration, site tracking and reporting of aggregate usage information to our marketing and product development teams. 

Volar Video, Inc. may use this information to administer its site and analyze overall trends. The information that this Web Site automatically gathers, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors, helps determine how much visitors use parts of the Web Site, so that Volar Video, Inc. can make improvements. Volar Video, Inc. may also provide aggregated statistical “ratings” information, never information about Users personally, to its partners about how visitors collectively use the site.

From time to time, Volar Video, Inc. may solicit your opinion to determine your preferences and dislikes in order to provide you with a better product. These surveys are always optional to the user and your decision not to participate in a survey will not affect your status as a Volar Video Web Site user. Should you choose to participate, any information you give us may be used in aggregate form for marketing purposes, and to enhance your overall experience on our site.

### 4\. With whom the information may be shared

Volar Video, Inc. will not provide any personally identifiable information about you to other third parties without your consent. Volar Video, Inc. may, however, provide other third parties with anonymous aggregated information about our users to illustrate trends and patterns.

### 5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information

If you are to be sent further offers as part of a contest entry, you will be clearly notified (such as an SLFC contest). Volar Video, Inc. will not share your information with any other parties other than those clearly listed when you give us your information. For instance, if SLFC sponsors a contest with Volar Video, only SLFC and Volar Video will collect your information. No other third parties will have access.

### 6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control

Volar Video has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. The servers for Volar Video, Inc. are stored in a physically secure and climate controlled off-site facility. Beyond the physical protection of the servers, we protect against data loss by regularly backing up data, performing consistency checks with independently recorded log files to prevent tampering, and restricting access to information on our servers via several user authentication technologies. Only those employees needed to carry out the business functions will have access to information on individual Volar Video customers.

We train each such employee with respect to the Volar Video Privacy Policy, and those violating these policies will be subject to disciplinary action.

It is important to remember that whatever you transmit or disclose online can be collected and used by others or unlawfully intercepted by third parties. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. In addition, we may disclose information to law enforcement or other government officials if we determine such disclosure to be appropriate, or if we are compelled to disclose it by court order or operation of law.

NOTE TO PARENTS

It is Volar Video, Inc.'s policy not to solicit any personally identifiable information from children. All Volar Video, Inc. online registrants will be required to enter their full name, age, zip code and e-mail address. If Volar Video, Inc. determines that a person is under the age of 13, based on the information provided during the registration process, that person will not be permitted to register online for our contests or offers in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. Any personally identifiable information that the child may have attempted to enter during the registration process will not be collected or maintained by Volar Video. Children who indicate that they are under 13 years old will not be able to make credit card purchases or participate in interactive features on Volar Video, Inc. that involve the collection and retention of personal information (e.g., entering a sweepstakes).

Volar Video, Inc. works with (and may provide links to) third party sites that offer features described on Volar Video, Inc. Such third parties may permit children under the age of 13 to register for these features on their sites in accordance with their respective privacy policies. For more information, please review the privacy policies of each respective third party site. Volar Video does not knowingly obtain, retain or use information from anyone who indicates that they are under 13 years old.

NOTE ON ADVERTISERS

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here

Volar Video, Inc. reserves the right to periodically revise this policy. In the event we modify our policy, we will give reasonable notice. Since notice of any such policy will not appear on our website indefinitely, and may only be posted for a limited time, it will be incumbent upon you to check our Privacy Policy regularly to see if we have made any modifications.

LAST UPDATED: November 21, 2014

Copyright 2014 Volar Video, Inc. All rights reserved.
